goresults.net 2015-10-11

# GoResults.Net - Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions

The Privacy Policy described below is with respect to our use and protection of any personal information you provide to us through the www.goresults.net website .This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which **e4e Labs Pvt. Ltd**. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the  [http://goresults.net/](http://goresults.net/)  website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by **goresult.net.**

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the exam results alerts, Notifications, exam news updates, exam calendars, newsletter etc.., fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name and version, the type of computer ,Mobile Phone, Tablet models and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the type of operating system & version and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience.  We use cookies for redirection to concerned region User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use the collected information**

e4e Labs Pvt. Ltd. may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To improve customer service -_ Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

  * _To personalize user experience -_ We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

  * _To improve our Site -_ We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

  * _To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature -_ To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics articles, Newsletters we think will be of interest to them.

  * _To send periodic emails -_ If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include Breaking News, company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Information security**

  * We take appropriate security measures to the best of our capacity, to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.

  * Only very few of our employees might have restricted access to some of personal data only if it requires them to use it in order to fulfill what Users/Customers ordered or requested. This is required to offer a quality service from us. 

**Sharing your personal information**

We sell, trade, lease, exchange, rent Users personal identification information to any entity (business, agencies, individuals). We may share generic aggregated demographic information (a group or a set) which is not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertisements or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at  [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

**Changes to this privacy policy**

e4e Labs Pvt. Ltd. has the sole discretion to update this privacy policy at any time without any prior notice. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
[http://e4elabs.com](http://e4elabs.com/). ,http://goresults.net  
29, 5th Cross, 35th Main, BTM 2nd Stage, Bangalore-68  
91-80-49547799  
info@goresults.net

This document was last updated on April 24, 2015
